KYLE HARRISON

Baltimore, MD • 706-264-0149 • kyleharrison687@gmail.com • www.linkedin.com/in/kyle-harrison-data-analytics

SUMMARY

I have a diverse career history that has led to my current role as Shelf-Set Coordinator. I've spent the last few years working in off-premise sales in the alcoholic beverage industry. Previously, I spent time in manufacturing and gained three years of management experience. I learned notable skills like welding, pipefitting and obtained a CDL.

SKILLS

• Excel

Tableau Python

Power BiWord

Management

• SQL

EXPERIENCE

Eagle Rock Distribution, Calhoun, GA **Shelf-Set Coordinator** (Jan 2024 – Present)

Jan 2021 – Present

- Led the scheduling and execution of both large and small format chain account resets for the Northwest Georgia
- Used Power Bi and Excel to build and implement a tracker used by our company to monitor the completion of key surveys performed by our account managers in the trade
- Worked closely with Anheuser Busch Analytics to create reports that were used by our sales management team to target distribution and volume goals for account managers
- Used data analysis from Space Planning Plus to create merchandising plans for independent stores that targeted products and space to maximize sales

Account Manager (Jan 2021 - Dec 2023)

- Analyzed sales data and inventory levels in large and small format off premise accounts to place accurate orders for my customers
- Generated sales to meet monthly, quarterly, and yearly goals by communicating with customers to make sure they always had a generous supply of existing and trending products.

EZ Carpet, Dalton, Ga

Mar 2018 – Dec 2020

Production and Sales Manager

- Coordinated the production of peel and stick carpet tile
- Managed a team that was tasked with the marketing and online sell of carpet tiles using online marketplaces like Amazon, Wayfair, and Shopify
- Created sales reports and maps to present to the company's ownership to show the success and viability of the company

Mohawk Industries Dalton, Ga

Jan 2011 – Feb 2018

Shift Supervisor

• Oversaw 40+ employees and the production of twisted and heat-set yarn

General Maintenance

Performed major repairs to heat-set lines some of which included welding and pipe fitting

EDUCATION

Data Analytics Accelerator Boot Camp

June 2024 - Present

Georgia Southern University, Statesboro, Ga

Aug 2004 – May 2005

Dalton High School, Dalton, Ga

Sep 2001 – May 2004